
Sample stylesheets til display af Danske Efaktura

html.xsl kan bruges standalone, override.xsl imports html.xsl og viser nogle genbruges muligheder. Override.xsl uses the table based layout of økonomistyrelsen's fakturaprint. html.xsl uses basic css based layout. 
there are two example html displays: invoiceresult.html which is generated using html.xsl, and invoiceresult2.html which is generated using override.xsl.

There are two css files, ubl.css and finance.css, finance.css is blank, it's just there so that people could edit that css to change particular displays. 

Most everything has been changed to being css class and id based displays. 



fo.xsl er blevet testet med fop, fo.xsl imports fonamedtemplate.xsl


version 0.10